Hello everyone, I am Huang Maihang from the Chinese Academy of Fine Arts.
I am now a senior fashion designer.
I am very happy to be able to come to the live broadcast.
Thank you for the invitation.
Let me introduce myself first.
I graduated from Guangzhou Academy of Fine Arts.
I am now studying the fashion design major at the Chinese Academy of Fine Arts.
In addition to the fashion design, I also like to broaden my interests.
I am very interested in photography and makeup, which are related to fashion.
At the same time, I am also very inspired by my design.
Let me share some of my personal works.
These are some of my previous makeup works.
You can see that I like to use very vivid colors.
For example, the color of silver and light.
Or the color of silver and light.
I like to use contrasting colors to express the sense of conflict.
I rarely use black and white colors in my design.
On the left is a work of mine that I used to make.
On the right is a work of mine that I used to make.
They all have the same style as my makeup.
I would like to show you some of my previous works.
My previous design works have a strong connection with the projects that I am going to introduce.
My design style has always been like this.
It has a huge impact on my 3D work.
I would like to show you some of the works that I made during my studies at the Chinese Academy of Fine Arts.
This is the first one.
There are two parts to this student course.
The first is for individual projects and the second is for group projects.
This is the first Collex 93 3D 3D 3D wear I use.
I use the combination between the Collex 94 and Collex 90+.
This is another combination of Collex 94 and Collex 95%.
But this class has a total of seven weeks, about two months. I can't just do a little bit.
Then I can show you a more explosive video. It's made by me and my team members.
I don't know what to do.
I'm going to show you the whole thing.
Two Monte Faciliti.
Six.
One.
Thank you for watching.
Okay, after watching the video, I believe everyone will still be shocked by this color, because I basically used all the colors I could use, and I basically didn't use any black or white, except for the teeth, which are white.
So you can see that there are some tooth elements in it. This is also an inspiration for the project I will talk about later.
So let me introduce how this course is set up in the school.
So this course is about seven weeks, which is a total of 49 days.
And then it's divided into individual and group.
Individuals can find their own design style in the early stages and quickly learn the basic skills.
And then the group part can let students get better connections and learn better group cooperation.
And then how to go.
Within the two main
after.
Then what?
The most important thing is that in addition to Closed 3D,
there are also AIGC applications and multi-application mixed applications,
including Nomade, Blender, TouchDesigner, and other combinations.
So the ability points to be covered in this short seven-week period are actually very wide.
In other words, as a fashion designer,
my favorite photography and my favorite makeup
have all turned from traditional to virtual.
In fact, it is a very connected and innovative way.
This is a big step forward for me, and it's a brand new experience.
Next, I would like to talk about the inspiration and the source of my theme and inspiration for this project.
In fact,
Many people are more afraid of pain, including myself, because I used to have a long time of lonely time, even though it's over now, but this long time of loneliness has actually had a very big impact on my life, because it is accompanied by a long time of pain and discomfort, so you have to adapt to it slowly in life, accept it, so you have to accept it.
When I share this kind of pain, I don't want it to be a very painful feeling, because you think you will only do something with something every day because you are happy, so if you want to be happy, you might as well use a happier way to transfer it.
So I basically used a lot of happy colors, for example, a lot of contrast colors, such as red and green, or yellow and purple.
Thoughlit its way of expression is unpleasant, but having a lot of colors will also make someone feel numb or a little uncomfortable
That is the kind of visual style that I want to explore.
So I taken a look at some of the styles that I mentioned above, and
The first one is Pe übrigens,risking to 예 scene
The famous Asian culture that Latino alcoholies love
is called
Pe
It expresses its own existence through the teeth.
And then there is Acid Wave.
The most powerful point of its style is that it uses a lot of colors,
a lot of bumpy colors to mix them together,
and then it forms a kind of acidic feeling,
which is visually very messy, very messy,
and gives people a sour feeling.
At the same time, it is also a style of music.
And the last one is Eye Spy.
I believe that everyone, including my generation,
must have seen the visual discovery.
In fact, it is the original version of the visual discovery,
which is Eye Spy.
There are many small scenes in it,
very delicate and rich.
There will be a little poem below
to let you find the treasure in this scene.
I hope that the video and the scene I can make
can also have such delicacy
and this kind of discovery.
So I think it is also a very important reference for me.
So in the previous video,
you also saw the characters,
which are these four.
They are Door Tooth, Tiger Tooth, Old Tooth, and Sting Tooth.
The first red character is Tiger Tooth,
which is Full Tooth.
Why?
Because Tiger Tooth is the teeth that we need to stand out the most
and refuse the most out of our mouths.
So it is the sharpest and sharpest.
So the image and design I gave him
is also a more pungent and avant-garde sharpness.
Then the second one is Door Tooth.
Why is there a suit in the Door Tooth?
Because Door Tooth is the first tooth in your mouth.
The first tooth that can be seen at the beginning.
So it's like a front of the door.
If the front of the door is crooked,
people won't think that the front of the door is crooked.
So I want to give the front of the door a more formal feeling.
So I put on a suit for her.
Although I didn't give her a very overall feeling,
I want to give her a more complete feeling.
The top of the hat is also a change of the dress.
It's a change of the dress.
So I made it more like a tooth.
It will be more fun.
The third one is the old tooth.
The old tooth is a big tooth.
It's in the middle of the tooth.
It acts as a bite.
It's a point of bite.
And it's very big.
All my clothes,
I made a lot of elements and inspirations from the image of the old tooth.
And then I put the bite on the clothes to simulate this state.
And then the second tooth.
Why is it a child?
Because the second tooth actually grows out when a person is mature.
So the age of her teeth is actually the smallest of all kinds.
So we set it up for her to be a smart, lively, and cute child.
This is a very strange feeling.
So through my introduction,
you can probably guess that each tooth has a different character.
So what we want to do is to adapt to the characters' character by tooth.
Add the characters' character that people will encounter in real life.
So the next is the most important part,
which is the application and landing of technology.
I think the best experience of Clover 3D is that it is a very efficient tool.
Of course, this is obvious.
Look at the picture on my right. This is some of the process of playing the board and some of the materials.
In Clover, you can greatly reduce your learning cost.
You can try it out very quickly without worrying about whether it will really work.
Because you need to try it out first and then slowly make it work.
So I think this is a very good tool.
Just like what the teacher just said, they often use this to make a sketch during project development.
So I think it is a very good tool.
And I think it is also very free.
For example,
the one on my right is actually a round set of tiger teeth.
So I gave it to Blender and re-dye it.
But it is actually still Clover.
In fact, normal cloth is very difficult to achieve this kind of shine and this kind of exquisite feeling.
That is,
you can try a very rich material combination on it.
And you can have some dynamic display.
Like a video of a personal project I just put in front of me.
That's how it came.
And then you can try some of the crafts you have never tried in real life.
I think it's also very OK.
Of course, the next is a very important point.
It is to master this technology.
In fact, it is also a very good tool for students.
It is a very delicious skill.
Because now there are many industries,
not only in clothing design,
but also in the game industry.
In fact, it has also started.
It should not be considered a start.
But it has been there for a long time.
It also starts to need the design of game clothing very much.
And then it also needs the skill of this kind of 3D software.
So it will be close 3D.
In fact, it is very good.
It is also very important in the future.
Including not only close 3D,
but also Blender,
and even Nomad.
Other 3D tools are also very important.
Because it is also very convenient to communicate.
For example, if you communicate with the tablet,
it is very difficult to add or subtract here and there.
In fact, it is very difficult to get it all at once.
But you can use close 3D very quickly.
It is equivalent to using the same set of grammar to say the same thing.
And then,
the problems in the process,
there are actually quite a lot of problems.
One is,
because I studied from 0 to 1.
So I started,
because it is from real money to virtual money.
In fact, there are still some difficulties.
I will have a little bit of contact.
Because I don't know which action corresponds to this function in real life.
So sometimes I feel a little bit
I don't know how to use
some of those functions.
But this is actually familiar.
But there is also that it is easy to pierce and tear.
For example, my tablet is actually very wide.
I want to inflate it inside.
So in fact, in real life,
we either inflate it or inflate it.
In fact, the concept of parameter simulation in the computer
is equivalent to saying that the pressure on both sides is the same.
It can only ensure that one is a balance force.
Otherwise, it will dry out or float away.
So I used to,
because my clothes were inflated,
so I often would,
the clothes would float away.
This is also a point where you have to practice more
so that you will not make mistakes.
There is also a gravity and physical properties.
This is actually the thing about the fabric.
If this fabric is not suitable for this property,
then I think it can be
that you have to try more different fabrics.
This might be a little better.
Then on the right is a design of a very simple leg cover.
In fact, it is the same in real life.
It needs a elastic band to tie it up.
So it also needs a board like this in Claw.
So I think that in fact, after using Claw,
it took me,
it made the connection between 2D and 3D in my real life
is actually stronger.
Because I know one thing,
what it should look like when it is flat.
But when it is three-dimensional,
what it looks like on the human body,
it will connect better.
And then,
but it has a bad,
it's not bad,
it's just a difficulty.
It's just that I was easy to sew wrong.
In fact, it is in real life,
a counter-strike,
this kind of,
or counter-strike,
the sewing concept is actually the same.
But it's just in 3D,
it's easy to see it wrong,
or there are some technical operations that are not familiar with it,
leading to this mistake.
This is a mistake I often make,
at the beginning.
Yes.
And then the third one is the most important.
It's not just Claw 3D anymore.
You can see this screenshot of me.
At the top,
there are Blender,
GLTF,
MTL,
F2K,
and other methods.
And then the third one is a,
called,
a pattern.
Various patterns.
Because my workflow is like this.
I need to build clothes in Claw,
go to Nomad,
adjust models,
and also do the accessories,
build models,
and then go to Blender,
to render,
after rendering,
in,
in the scene,
render in Blender,
and then send it to the AI to generate the video.
So there are actually a lot of steps.
So you need to know which software
is compatible with which format of file.
You must remember very clearly.
Otherwise, it will often...
For example, I once went from Nomade to Blender,
or Blender to Nomade.
I forgot.
But it's easy to lose data,
or some of the materials I built in Close 3D
are worn out or damaged.
Look at this person on my right.
After I imported it,
the material has deformed.
So I need to go back to Close 3D to do it again.
It would actually be a waste of time.
Yes, and another point is the AI generation part.
You can see these four squares.
These four squares are what I used
to create the face of this person on the right.
I needed to give him a very long description
so that he could give me a picture
that I even thought was only 70% accurate.
So I think he needs to spend some time training.
So what I recommend is Nanobanana.
I think Nanobanana is...
I think Nanobanana is the smartest AI
because whatever you say,
it will say what you say very cleverly.
Mage Journey has its own ideas.
It will add things on its own.
So this AI also requires you to spend a lot of time training.
And the premise is that you have a certain aesthetic
and a certain design thinking in it.
And then the last one is,
each software uses a different way of working.
So you need to be very clear about what each software is doing.
Otherwise, it's easy to mix and match.
And then...
But this is also related to the division of work in the project.
At that time, some of us were doing clothing and makeup.
Some of us were making videos.
Some of us were making scenes.
That's how it works.
And then you can take a look.
This is a picture of me creating a configuration
and adjusting the model in Nomad.
In fact, Nomad is also quite good when combined with Close 3D.
Because Nomad is actually...
It's like you can pinch it with your hand.
It's like a sculpture.
You can pinch it with your hand.
It's more direct.
If there are some hard materials,
I can use Nomad to combine them.
And it can also...
It can also have some pre-generated rendering.
For example, the one on my left is very colorful.
It's a rendering of the lighting.
I think it's pretty cool.
And then I went to Blender to render this.
I adjusted this face in Nomad.
But the model source is the model in Close 3D.
And then this is a picture of me.
Because I made it with Close 3D,
I need to do some post-processing to inspire how to make a video or a more powerful visual effect.
So I'm on the left.
This should be a GLB.
It's an effect that's directly opened in the Apple computer.
It will have a kind of 7P effect.
Yeah, I think it's pretty good.
And then on the right is me.
Before I made the video,
I used some pictures to make some post-processing.
And then this...
This is another workflow for me.
This is a workflow for makeup.
It also has to make makeup in Blender first,
and then render it out with Blender.
You can take a look at this rendering.
This is what's rendered in Blender
and what's rendered in Nanobanana.
Because if I want to render in Blender...
First of all, because I'm a zero-based learner,
it's very difficult for me to get a very detailed rendering at once.
And it takes a lot of time.
It takes a lot of time to render a single image.
It takes a lot of hours.
And then I use Nanobanana to get it out quickly.
I just need to give it a hint.
I want a real human face.
I want to maintain the makeup the same.
Everything else remains the same.
But the texture and texture of the face must be very real.
And then it can come out like this.
It's actually very suitable for the role I'm thinking of.
And then on the left,
I put this picture
to this...
Tab Now.
Oh, no, this is already in Tab Now.
It's equivalent to it having a node in Tab Now,
and then it generates a script of my video.
I know how to edit a video.
I know the logic and the connection between each picture and each picture.
And then finally,
I use Kling to generate a video.
Because Tab Now is a little expensive.
The gold coin I tried in the previous period
actually didn't have a lot of gold coins.
Because I have to make a long video
for at least three to five minutes.
So I used Kling.
It's a little cheaper.
The effect is also good.
And then you can see
that there are actually a lot of drafts.
And then you need to consider
a lot of pre and post-connections.
And how to shoot this scene.
And the relationship between this character
and this scene.
Is it in the middle or on the side?
Is the camera facing up or down?
Where is this from?
Is this a sports perspective or a fixed perspective?
So these are all very necessary
for some visual accumulation.
This is a more comprehensive ability.
It's like a director's perspective.
Look at this picture.
So I think
this class
brings me a lot of things.
This is some screenshots.
These are some scenes.
Screenshots including clothes,
some empty screenshots.
The most right
is all the makeup.
This is some makeup
that is very difficult to achieve in reality.
And then I did a lot of
super-realistic things.
Whether it's clothes,
character's style,
and the scene.
And then the final
thing I want to say is
because I used to be
a fashion designer.
The reason why I chose fashion
is because I really love
handcrafted things.
I think handcrafted things
are more lively and have more vitality.
But
later on
I started from a computer
and learning techniques
to now
I'm very passionate about learning these techniques.
I have experienced a lot of psychological struggle.
But I found that
as long as you take this step
to learn,
you will have a very good result.
You can try more things
that you didn't dare to think of before.
But what I want to say is
in terms of learning techniques,
for example,
AI is very popular now.
I think original things
are very important.
You have to have an original idea
to make something good.
Otherwise,
it's easy to be taken by
some big trends.
It's hard to form your own style.
Besides AI,
learning techniques itself
is also very important.
Whether it's the most basic
clothing sewing
or the electronic
close 3D virtual sewing,
I think these are all very important.
Because you know this technique
and you know how to realize it better.
While learning techniques,
it's also very important to
maintain the subjectivity.
This way,
you won't be drowned in the age of AI.
OK, this is my sharing.
Thank you, everyone.